This is Guys Wires Balram and She Defined
Investment Advisor Channel, so today
in this video we are going to talk about the bank and if you do
not know the details then along with watching this video, do
subscribe to this channel, so let's
start it, first of all let's
talk about HDFC Bank
because here we are going to
review the results of the consolidated fund, in which
this time i.e. for
March 2018, here we have
tomato and this brinjal which is 2036 which is in the last
and always 100 500,
you will see that near here there is arrowroot
of 110 crores, due to this
we have a lot of total income here,
quarter and share and here it was almost
compared to last year,
you can see a handsome growth here,
due to this we are able to
incur a little less overall total expenditure here,
if we talk about operating
profit then there is a very good earning in it,
which this time we have to zinc road,
last year this figure was 3000  Profit more than 1000,
profit 1000, which is a
slight decline compared to the previous quarter,
we are showing here, but if we
compare it with last year, then for this
you will get almost 100% profit. If we talk about
some important scenes here, then
you will have to search here, so here I will do a
little bit of it and if we see it
in a video here, then this
time these two quotes in the last one are very fast, in this
we have a 70% profit,
see here and half a minute 10 points,
this result is quite good, but this, which
we have seen a slight decline here, or
if we talk about 60 in the city, if we compare it
with last year, then in this
you will see almost
or VAT question's profit, but for
now we are giving you 50% total, so this thing is
quite good compared to last year and the previous year, that
this time we have seen a very good miscellaneous income
and even if we look at the investment
here, here we have to fly and here
if the profit and in this you will see  You will
get it, which means you will get it compared to the previous quarter
and here you can see, so
if you subscribe to one of these schools, let's say
some important antique
Kalpavriksha, angry bird, then 2.5 and
its clear 1000 E
that I and rickshaws took here Bodh quarter
and this lipstick has had a positive
impact, I shared personal here,
see here, the investment that my
company has received has reduced a bit,
but because of this net profit growth,
you have porn here, now
this video with school, but if we talk, then do it here
and on various internet sites,
if you want to stock here, this tempered glass, then there will be a
little up shadow in it, just
because of pure pink cancer, after opening here,
you can get 1 to 2% in the market and
in that you can join this video here and
if you have not yet joined
this win positional and multi Venkat Reddy is the
founder, then you should join him if
you have heard about all those teachers
in the next video,
Ajay
Is